Their graduation present was a trip to paradise, but they
never thought they would land in hell.
Brokedown Palace is a drama, thriller, mystery film directed by Jonathan Kaplan.
Best friends Alice and Darlene take a trip to
Thailand after graduating high school.
In Thailand, they meet a captivating Australian
man, who calls himself Nick Parks.
Darlene is particularly smitten with Nick and convinces Alice to take Nick up on his
offer to treat the two of them to what amounts to a day trip to Hong Kong.
In the airport, the girls are seized by the police and shocked to
discover that one of their bags contains heroin.
Alice Marano, played by Claire Danes.
Darlene Davis, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Hank Greene, played by Bill Pullman.
Yon Greene, played by Jacqueline Kim.
Roy Knox, played by Lou Diamond Phillips.
Nick Parks, played by Daniel Lapaine.
Brokedown Palace is a 1999 American drama film directed by Jonathan Kaplan,
and starring Claire Danes, Kate Beckinsale, and Bill Pullman.
It deals with two American friends imprisoned in
Thailand for alleged drug smuggling.
Its title is taken from a Grateful Dead song written by Jerry Garcia
and Robert Hunter from their 1970 album American Beauty.
The film explores themes of prison, thailand, vacation, drugs, injustice.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.